<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on D Wilson Blog</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on D Wilson Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 19:23:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I stumbled my way into learning Websockets</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/websocketsbasics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 19:23:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/websocketsbasics/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a Golang kick recently. After hearing all the cool kids talk about it, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn everything about it. Along with that, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn new/interesting concepts that Golang can be used for, particularly focusing on stuff I suck at.&#xA;Web development is one such area. I hate Javascript. It gives me the ick-ies. But, I hear of these wonderful Golang packages that let us do so much without having to touch a line of stinking JS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Sudoku Solver in Golang</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/golangsudoku/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:38:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/golangsudoku/</guid>
      <description>I used to like playing Sudoku. I used to have an app on my phone that would let me play Sudoku. I mostly used it during class whenever I was bored. I ended up getting to a point with the app where I ended up stuck on the really hard board, and I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure it out. True Sudoku fans may tell you it&amp;rsquo;s all about skill. In truth, it&amp;rsquo;s really a truly simple algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hugo or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Static Site Generation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/hugo-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 19:40:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/hugo-basics/</guid>
      <description>When I first started my blog shortly after graduating from college, I thought it would be so cool to make it myself. What does make it yourself mean? Well, I found a premade HTML template online, plugged in some pictures, changed some of the words, and let it rip.&#xA;It sucked. Both practically, in the sense that it looked lke shit, and as a portfolio, in the sense that it looked like shit and it didn&amp;rsquo;t demonstrate anything about my skills.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
